i have had an amazing
year
uh big news can you see that right there
look at that
oh my gosh
thank you my grandmother died
and um
it took forever do you know what i mean
98 i'm like okay go to the light nana
good golly you're holding on lady you've
lived a life
really pops in here look at that light
watch your retinas you cute little
biscuits
no some of you got sad don't get sad
she's not dead that's a horrible thing
to say i would never
say that um she's confused i took it
right off her hand
old people
no that's not nice either oh you got so
sad that's not nice she's dead don't
worry she's dead um
what a roller coaster of emotion
i didn't kill her she um
just felt like i should say that you
know what i mean like adorable but
yeah no i just celebrated a five-year
wedding anniversary i've been married
for five years
yeah
just so you know little little self
reflection for you all you applauded and
laughed harder when my grandmother died
i just wanted you i
just want you to know that you know what
i mean just look to yourself for some
growth
married to a man who is very kind and
very nice and i like him a lot
um i'm smitten one might say
um
i'm an older bride
first time being married not gonna do it
again i wouldn't suggest it
um he's been married before
and that didn't work out so good so more
evidence that someone else's trash is
another person's treasure am i right
reduce reuse recycle uh
he's like a nice pair of goodwill jeans
you know what i mean like really broken
in like you can full squat and um couple
stains suspicious smell febreze we're
good to go
go he's cozy i love him
it's good stuff it's funny when you get
married later or you find someone later
you're looking for things that are
different than when you're younger right
you're a very young hot crowd i don't
know if that's appropriate but i said it
[Laughter]
[Applause]
you know what i mean like i don't want
to hit on you but
as a collective whole looking good nice
work
yeah yeah to you um
[Music]
[Laughter]
i have a niece who's 20. this is how she
talks about the love of her life
if we were to two
amoebas and we were floating around and
like
finding each other in the universe like
we would like found each other if we
were
i don't even know what she's talking
about
i'm like what
what
what if you were an amoeba what are you
talking about
when you're in your 40s you're like so
do you have dental i'm just curious
if you have dental insurance
because i heard most people north of 40
need a crown are crowns covered on your
insurance
my teeth are great now but i don't know
you